{
	"namethatshow": [
        {
            "Question": "A 2006 Sitcom About A Self-Help Author Named Emily Who Is Inept At Her Own Love Life",
            "Answer": "Emily’s Reasons Why Not"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A 2011 Comedy About A Father Can’t Get His Grown Children To Leave Home",
            "Answer": "Regular Joe"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Cartoon About Three Anthropomorphic Toads Named After Skin Conditions: Rash, Zitz, And Pimple",
            "Answer": "Battletoads"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Comedy About A Book Editor And Her Friends And Co Workers At The Publishing House",
            "Answer": "Open Books"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Comedy About Parents Who Are Too Involved In Their Adult Children’s Lives",
            "Answer": "Happiness Isn’t Everything"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Comedy About Three Single Women Who Are Gifted A Rent-Free Year In A Swanky Manhattan Penthouse",
            "Answer": "Princesses"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Comedy Centered On A Mom Who Is Passionate About Her Domestic Inventions",
            "Answer": "Patent Pending"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Comedy From The Point Of View Of A Teenage Son Whose Father Comes Out As Gay",
            "Answer": "Don’t Ask"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Comedy Series About A Charismatic Dad Who Is Only Nineteen Years Older Than His Adult Son",
            "Answer": "Like Father"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Comedy Series Based On A Book Of Strange And Humorous Family Portraits",
            "Answer": "Awkward Family Photos"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Comedy Series Based On A British Format About A Recovering Alcoholic",
            "Answer": "Never Better"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Comedy Series Centered Around Two Couples That Are Turning Forty",
            "Answer": "Best Thing Ever"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Comedy Series Centered On A Family In Which Every Member Has Obsessive Compulsive Disorder",
            "Answer": "Bonkers"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Comedy Series Dealing With Interracial Relationships",
            "Answer": "Maybe It’s You"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Comedy Series Inspired By Mindy Weiss, One Of The Country’s Most Sought After Event Planners And Lifestyle Experts",
            "Answer": "Plan This"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Comedy Starring A Stand-Up Comedian About A Middle-Aged Advertising Executive And His Wife And Two Sons",
            "Answer": "Life… Stuff"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Coming-Of-Age Comedy About A Woman In Her Mid-Twenties And Her Desire To Orgasm",
            "Answer": "Thanks For Coming"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Couple Attempts To Maintain Their Hipster Childless Lifestyle Even Though They Now Have A Baby",
            "Answer": "Stroller Wars"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Couple From Nyc Move To The Husband’s Hometown Of Dallas",
            "Answer": "Big D"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Dad Creates A Robot But The Family Keeps It A Secret Pretending She’s Part Of The Family",
            "Answer": "Small Wonder"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Divorced Couple Live Near Each Other In Order To Share Custody Of Their Children",
            "Answer": "It’s Not Easy"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Family Of Mobsters Attempt To Transition Into A Legitimate Business",
            "Answer": "Unmade"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Family With Four Boys And Their Life In A Two Bedroom Apartment In Nyc",
            "Answer": "Didn’t I Feed You Yesterday"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Female Chemist Works At A Pharmaceutical Company Where The Social Life Is Like High School",
            "Answer": "Pharmville"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Group Of Single Mothers In An Apartment Building Help One Another Raise Their Teenage Sons And Daughters.",
            "Answer": "Milf \u0026 Cookies"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Group Of Young Investment Bankers All Get Fired On On The Same Day And Must Rethink Their Lives",
            "Answer": "Canned"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Lifetime Reality Series Following The Owners Of A Family Mortuary In Texas",
            "Answer": "Good Grief"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Man And Woman Agree To A Blind Date That Ends With The Woman Becoming Pregnant",
            "Answer": "Lucky Us"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Man Catches The Only Woman He Has Ever Loved Cheating On Him And Decides To Skip Town For A Better One",
            "Answer": "Awesometown"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Man Is Dumped By His Girlfriend And Ends Up Being Placed In The Cubicle Next To Hers",
            "Answer": "Hot Mess"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Man Of Mexican Descent Marries A Blonde Hillbilly And Raise Their Children In Rural Kentucky",
            "Answer": "Hick-spanic"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Man Realizes That His Business Partner, Who Is Also His Best Friend From College, Is The Perfect Woman For Him",
            "Answer": "Oh Fk, It’s You"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Man Recovers From The Death Of His Fiancee With The Help Of The Men On His Pick-Up Basketball Team",
            "Answer": "Rebounding"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Married Couple Killed In A Car Accident Return To Haunt Their Home",
            "Answer": "Nearly Departed"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Midwestern Girl Named Sonny Wins A Talent Search And Moves To La To Star In A Tv Show",
            "Answer": "Sonny With A Chance"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Peek Into The Workings Of A Private Practice Where A Pediatrician, Internist, And An Ob/Gyn Share The Same Roof",
            "Answer": "This Might Hurt"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Pro Golfer With Little Success Returns Home To Work At The Family Barbershop With His Father",
            "Answer": "Cutters"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Professor With The Ability To Turn Himself Into Any Animal Helps The Police Solve Crimes",
            "Answer": "Manimal"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Reality Show Parody In Which A Camera Follows Two Police Officers As They Face Crimes And Deal With Their Family Lives",
            "Answer": "Arresting Behavior"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Series Created For The Wb About A Man’s Life As An Au Pair",
            "Answer": "Commando Nanny"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Show Following Two Brothers On Adventures Involving Wresting And Air Guitar",
            "Answer": "The Mullets"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Single Mother In Her Thirties Decides That Finding Love Is Her Priority",
            "Answer": "Tick Tock"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Sitcom About Volunteer Firemen",
            "Answer": "Where’s The Fire?"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Sitcom In Shich Two Men Fly Around And Have Adventures In A Winged Car Starship",
            "Answer": "Homeboys In Outer Space"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Sketch Comedy Show Of Shorts Featuring Improv Stars From The Upright Citizens Brigade",
            "Answer": "This Show Will Get You High"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Slapstick Comedy Series About Two Brothers Who Were Janitors For Their Uncle’s Office Building",
            "Answer": "Working Stiffs"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Young Girl Discovers She Is Half-Alien",
            "Answer": "Out Of This World"
        },
        {
            "Question": "About A Stepbrother And Sister In Scottsdale, Arizona Who Own And Run A Gym In A Strip Mall",
            "Answer": "Sweat Shop"
        },
        {
            "Question": "An 80’S Sitcom Centered On A Fit Heath Club Owner And Two Attractive Aerobics Instructors",
            "Answer": "Shaping Up"
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Abc Comedy About Four Men Who Have Been Lifelong Friends And Are In The “Prime Of Life”",
            "Answer": "These Guys"
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Air Force Bachelor Is Asked To Care For A Sexy Female Robot",
            "Answer": "My Living Doll"
        },
        {
            "Question": "An All-Girls School Decides To Allow Boys To Attend",
            "Answer": "Co-ed Fever"
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Animated Comedy About A Dog With Issues Who Struggles With Jealously Towards His Human Family",
            "Answer": "Heel"
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Animated Comedy Centered On The Humor Of Comedian Brian Regan",
            "Answer": "Flyin With Brian"
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Animated Comedy Seriers About Two Brothers Living In A Fancy Gated Community",
            "Answer": "Sunflower Ponds"
        },
        {
            "Question": "An Early 90’S Sitcom About A New Music Teacher Who Is Assigned Four Troublemaking Students",
            "Answer": "Teech"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Andy Troutner, A Freshman Trying To Be The Most Popular Kid, Finds Himself In A Series Of Embarassing Situations",
            "Answer": "Go Fish"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cops Sing While Performing Legitimate Cop Work",
            "Answer": "Cop Rock"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Dick And Jane Have Just Started Dating And Are Very Unsure Of Their Relationship",
            "Answer": "Loves Me, Loves Me Not"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Four Former High School Championship Basketball Players Are Now In Their Forties And Dealing With Family Life",
            "Answer": "Champs"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Frank’s Every Move Literally Leads To Disaster",
            "Answer": "Don’t Bring Frank"
        },
        {
            "Question": "In This Modern-Day “Odd Couple” Comedy, We See Get A Peek Inside The Disturbing Minds Of Two Male Roommates",
            "Answer": "Peep Show"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Kids Accidentally Set Off A Nuclear Missile And The World Is Destroyed Except For Six People",
            "Answer": "Woops!"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Larry Is A 44-Year-Old Diverced Man Raising Two Teens And Hosting A Call-In Psychology Radio Show",
            "Answer": "Hello, Larry"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Set In Moscow, This 70’S Sitcom Was A Cold War-Era Satire Of Russian Life",
            "Answer": "Ivan The Terrible"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Set In Ohio, Three Men Decide It’s Time To Grow Up And Start Acting Their Age",
            "Answer": "Man Up!"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Sitcom Starring A Christian Comedian About Parents Whose Motto Is Family First, No Matter The Consequences",
            "Answer": "Bless This Mess"
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Adventures Of A Male Womanizer And His Friends",
            "Answer": "Confessions Of A Dog"
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Misadventures Of A Thirteen-Hundred-Year-Old Dragon Who Befriends A Single Dad And His Daughter",
            "Answer": "Scorch"
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Relationship Between Two Female Life-Long Friends Changes When One Of Them Gets Married",
            "Answer": "Ladyfriends"
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Story Of A Man Whose Mother Has Been Reincarnated As A 1928 Porter Automobile",
            "Answer": "My Mother The Car"
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Comedy Series Explores The Ways In Which Men And Women Perceive Situations Differently",
            "Answer": "He Said, She Said"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Three Families –One White, One Hispanic, And One African-American –Are Brought Together By Their Kids’ Sports Teams",
            "Answer": "Little In Common"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Three Female Friends Make It A Priority To Go Out Every Friday Night And A Have A Fun Time",
            "Answer": "Super Fun Night"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Two Chicago Teens Chase Their Dream Of Becoming Professional Dancers",
            "Answer": "Shake It Up!"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Two Friends Become Test Subjects For A Medical Company",
            "Answer": "Testees"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Two Married Attorneys Work Together In Their Own Office",
            "Answer": "Work With Me"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Two Obnoxious And Wealthy Friends Don’t Care About The Chaos They Create As They They Party Hard In Los Angeles",
            "Answer": "Rich Dicks"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Two Witty Social Misfits Deal With College Life While Working Part Time As Hired Assassins",
            "Answer": "Sparkle Death"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Uk Sitcom In Which Adolf Hitler And Eva Braun Live Nextdoor To A Stereotyped Jewish Family",
            "Answer": "Heil Honey I’m Home!"
        }
    ]
}